ladies and gentlemen you've heard all ladies and gentlemen you've heard all the
evidence I submit that this was not a Hot Blooded
Crime of Passion consider a Hot Blooded Crime of Passion consider this
a revolver holds Six Bullets not this a revolver holds Six Bullets not eight
that means he fired the gun empty and then stop
to reload by the power vested in Me by the
state of Maine I hereby order you to serve two
life sentences back to one for each of your victims
so
they send you here for life that's they send you here for life that's exactly
what they take I believe in two things discipline
help me and the Bible here you'll receive both Andy
came Bible here you'll receive both Andy came to sha
shank prison in to sha shank prison in 1947 why'd
you do it I didn't since you asked going to
fit right in I must admit didn't think much of
Andy first time my laid eyes on him he had
a quiet way about him a walk and talk that
a just wasn't normal around here there are just wasn't normal around here there are places
in the world that aren't made out
of stone there's something inside they stone there's something inside they can't
touch what you talking about Hope can't touch what you talking about Hope let
me tell you something my friend hope is a dangerous
thing damn it new friend you're putting thing damn it new friend you're putting me
behind hope can grab a man me behind hope can grab a man insane
you better be sick or dead in there I kid
you not better get used to that idea oh my
holy God I guess it comes down to a simple
Choice really get busy living you
dying get busy living or
dying that's damn